I'm Carly.
I'm on parole.
And this is...
The Web show watched by smart people...
And idiots.
You know which one you are.
Now before we do some of our pointless comedy...
We are gonna get
a little serious.
It's serious time.
Sam and I have been given
the opportunity to do
a real in-depth interview...
With one of America's
most important people.
So now, live via satellite, it's...
Aga-aahh-waabaa...
Now Jo Jo, our first question
is, how long have you been
a gigantic baby?
Aga-aahh-waabaa...
Jo Jo, how much do you weigh?
Waaahh! Baaahhh!
Okay I'm sorry.
I should not have asked that.
Aga-aahh.
And how do you feel
about the current state
of our nation's economy?
Aga-aahh-waabaa.
Insightful.
Aga-aahh-waabaa...
Yeah, all right.
How 'bout a hand for...
Okay, for the past few weeks
Sam, Freddie and I have been obsessed
with a certain chef on Food TV.
His name is Ricky Flame.
He's got this hot show
called "food fight"
where he shows up and challenges
people to a cook-off.
And Ricky always wins 'cause
he rocks food so hard.
True-- we love watching
Ricky Flame cook so much...
That it inspired us to do our
cooking segment here on iCarly.
We call it...
I thought of the name.
Uh-oh, your ear's all wet.
What are you talking about?
And my hatred grows stronger.
Will you turn the
camera this way please?
Okay, for our first "real"
iCarly cooking segment,
we're gonna make...
A dish invented by my brother Spencer...
Whose real name is Lateesha McPeanuts.
Yeah, no it's not.
So, all you need to make spaghetti
tacos are some taco shells...
Some spaghetti noodles
nyoodles, nyoodles.
Our secret sauce and meatballs.
Where are the meatballs?
Right about here, being
dissolved by my stomach acid.
While we make some more
meatballs, please enjoy this...
This has been a word from our Spencer.
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
[music]
♪ I know, you see ♪
♪ somehow the world ♪
♪ will change for me ♪
♪ and be so wonderful ♪
♪ live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow ♪
♪ we're gonna get there ♪
♪ and feel so wonderful ♪
♪ it's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ just how I feel ♪
♪ so wake up the members ♪
♪ of my nation ♪
♪ it's your time to be ♪
♪ there's no chance ♪
♪ unless you take one ♪
♪ and the time to see ♪
♪ the brighter side ♪
♪ of every situation ♪
♪ some things are meant to be ♪
♪ so give it your best ♪
♪ and leave the rest to me ♪
<font color="
www.addic7ed.com
All right, that should do her.
Cool, thanks Douglas.
Hey, no problem.
Oh, and hey, tell your mom I miss her.
Sure.
A lot.
I get it.
Hi, who was that?
Douglas, an electrician
who used to date my mom.
Oh.
I had him put a security
system in my locker.
So now if someone tries
to break into it,
they'll get blasted with like a
hundred volts of electricity.
Couldn't that really hurt someone?
I hope so.
Let's see what it does
to this knockwurst.
Ready?
Yeah.
Fry, baby.
Show me what you got.
Come on. Come on.
Yeah, that could hurt someone.
Or cook them to perfection.
Hey Sam.
What is that?
A charred knockwurst.
Yup.
I don't wanna know.
You borrowed my science
homework and I need it back.
Oh yeah.
Why don't you open my
locker and get it?
Fine.
No, don't do that!
Don't, don't.
We do not electrocute friends.
Hey, guys, something AMA--what's
that, a charred knockwurst?
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
I didn't wait, something
amazing just happened.
You ran here in your
robe and slippers.
No, I caught a ride from
some guy who sells pens.
Who needs pens?
...The green one?
What happened that's amazing?
Food TV called our house.
What?
Really?
They saw the last iCarly.
They wanna come do a show on you
guys about spaghetti tacos.
That's awesome.
We're gonna be on food TV.
But wait, spaghetti tacos
are your invention.
They should be interviewing you.
Nah! The important thing is
this will be great for iCarly.
Aah!
Oof!
Uh-oh. Argh argh!.
Here's some water.
Good.
Oh, thanks Freddie.
Ooh, uh-oh.
Sam feels really bad
about electrocuting you.
You know what?
It's okay.
You know why?
No.
Why?
'Cause when I got electrocuted,
just as I blacked out,
I experienced something incredible.
What, not dying?
Well, that and...
I had a vision of the future.
Look, you got shocked pretty bad.
Maybe you oughta-- I saw the future.
How do you know it was the future?
Because it hasn't happened yet.
Okay, what'd you see?
Well, it was hazy, but I saw
myself at the groovy smoothie
and that guy from galaxy
wars, nug nug was there,
and I saw him and me
together, hugging.
I'm calling Dr. Quamsteen.
No!
I gotta get to the groovy smoothie
and get my hug from nug nug.
Wait.
What?
What's nug nug from galaxy
wars gonna be doing
at the groovy smoothie in Seattle?
Hugging me.
I'm Sarah James, here with three
very popular Web celebrities.
Their names are Carly Shay, Sam
Puckett, and Freddie Benson,
better known as iCarly.
Hi.
Hey, food lovers.
So tell me about these
spaghetti tacos.
I'm Freddie Benson.
Well, one night my brother
Spencer couldn't decide
whether to make us spaghetti or tacos,
and so he combined 'em both
and invented spaghetti tacos.
And then later he taught
us how to make 'em.
Well, I hope he taught you
well, 'cause I'm Ricky Flame
and I challenge iCarly to...
What?
Oh my God!
Wait, we're on food fight right now?
Yes, you are.
Fantastico!
No way.
Awesome.
But how did you-- I watched you
guys make your spaghetti tacos
on iCarly and I wanna see
if I can make 'em better.
Cool, this is gonna be so fun.
Yeah.
What do we get if we win?
Well, I've never lost, but if you guys
are good enough to beat me,
you'll all win a one-year supply
of free steaks.
Yeah!
Wait, your definition of a
year supply or my definition?
She takes her meat very seriously.
Oh yes.
Hey man, what's your deal?
My deal?
You hung out here all day yesterday,
in your robe and slippers,
and all day today and you
haven't bought a thing.
I'm waiting for nug nug.
The dude from galaxy wars?
Yeah.
I had a vision of the
future where I saw nug nug
hugging me right here in the
middle of the groovy smoothie.
Cool.
Now, buy a smoothie or get out!
Oh yeah.
In my vision I was
drinking a smoothie.
Why don't you get me a
medium tingleberry blitz
and I'll watch the door.
Sounds like a plan.
Okay, this food fight is winding
down to a very exciting finish.
Ricky Flame and the iCarly
team are both putting
the final touches on
their spaghetti tacos.
Ricky's tacos look better than ours.
Yeah, his plating is exquisite.
Ten seconds left.
Okay, I'm doing it.
Where's the cheese?
Gimme the Peruvian puff peppers.
Right here, right here.
Sprinkle a handful of this.
Put it all over.
And time's up.
And now it's time for our
three judges to decide
whose spaghetti tacos reign supreme.
The plucky iCarly kids...
Plucky?
Plump and lucky?
Or super chef, Ricky Flame.
What is this?
My band-aid.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
She means her flavor patch.
Mm-hmm.
Excuse me, ma'am, I
really have to go pee,
but I'm expecting a small man
from outer space to come here.
His name is nug nug from
the planet Jueveron.
So would you mind waiting here,
and if you see nug nug come in,
just tell him I'll right back.
Crazy.
Uh-oh.
Hey, hey!
I hope you get space-jacked
by a flanch of red skynauts.
What?
It's galaxy wars talk.
Nerd.
You better run.
Judge Eric, your thoughts?
Well, I enjoyed all of these
spaghetti tacos, but with Ricky's,
I felt his flavors were just
layered more precisely.
So I have to cast my
vote for Ricky Flame.
Thank you, judge Eric.
I told you we should have layered
our flavors more precisely.
Judge Phillipe-- Ricky,
you never disappoint.
Your tacos were delicious, but your shells...
Are bit soggy.
As for the iCarly team, excellent
taste, original presentation.
I vote for iCarly.
Okay, judge Marla, it looks like
you have the deciding vote.
Come on Marla!
I'm so sorry.
You know, everyone here today
should feel proud of their tacos.
Chef Ricky, you're the
best, but I liked
the iCarly spaghetti tacos
just a little better.
Oh, my goodness.
For the first time
ever on "food fight,"
Ricky Flame has lost.
The iCarly's spaghetti tacos have won.
Congratulations, guys.
Gracias.
Yeah.
Where are my free steaks?
You'll get 'em.
Thank you.
Okay, that's it for this challenge.
Join us next time on...
Hey, I guess we just got lucky.
I lost.
Hey, can I have an autograph.
Later, please...
Unh!
He seems upset.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
I think your alarm system is on fire.
Nah, Franklin made me get
rid of my alarm system
'cause it kept blowin' fuses and
shortin' out the whole school.
The smoke's comin'
from my Gary Coleman grill.
You're cooking a steak in your locker?
Well, I'm not gonna eat raw meat
after what happened last time.
Stupid parasites.
Hey, listen.
I called Ricky's office,
you know, to thank him
for all the free steaks.
Yeah.
And his assistant told me
that he quit his TV show.
He's not doin'
"food fight" anymore?
anything anymore.
What, why?
Ricky's so depressed that he lost
to us, he said he's giving up
cooking forever.
It's not our fault Ricky went psycho.
Yeah, but come on, the least we
can do is go talk to the guy.
No the least we can do is nothing.
We're going to talk to Ricky.
Agreed.
Whatever.
But whatever happens, he still
owes us a full year's supply
of free steaks.
You know, there are more
important things in life
than free meat.
Yeah, not really.
[Knock on door]
Ricky...
Ricky.
I'm here with the iCarly kids.
Argh!
Come on in.
He's been like this ever
since he lost to you guys.
Argh!
[Alarm beeping]
I gotta take this.
Just try to cheer him up.
Ricky, come on.
So two out of three judges
liked our spaghetti tacos
better than yours.
Uh-oh.
Argh!
Unnecessary.
Don't you have some trick that
gets your mom out of bed.
Yeah.
Argh!
I'll try it.
Get up, ya lazy blob!
There's a cop at the door
and he's got a warrant!
...I'm a loser.
Here, gimme a hand.
Come on, come on, sit back--
that's there for a reason.
There you go.
There, don't you feel better now.
Yeah, I feel soooo great.
Well, you just need to get
outside and enjoy the sunshine
and fresh air.
Oh, Seattle.
Freddie, get the salad
stuff out of the cooler.
Okay.
This is dumb.
N it's not.
We just gotta remind Ricky
how much fun he has cooking.
Now sit him back up.
Come on Ricky.
Sit like a big boy.
I don't wanna sit.
I'm a loser.
You're not a loser.
You're just acting like one.
Remember that episode of
food fight where you went
to that lady's restaurant in
Cincinnati and you challenged her
to a salad war, and your salad
beat her salad and she cried?
Remember how great you felt.
Yeah, but that was my past.
No, you've still got it.
Now, come on and show
us how a real pro
makes a spicy flame-Bo salad
here's a big bowl of lettuce.
Augh.
Here's a cutting board...
And a Japanese cucumber.
Come now, take the knife.
Everybody loves a big sharp knife.
Yeah!
Big one, big slice.
Right.
Come on.
You can do it again.
Argh.
Aw, Ricky.
Your head's in the salad.
That's not good.
Ooooh.
Hey.
Hey-dude, mm.
We're closing u oh, yeah.
I was just waiting for someone.
Who?
Uh-- nothing.
It was stupid, I'll just...
Good night.
Hey, sorry guys, we're Clo-- whoa.
You're nug nug from galaxy wars.
What can I get ya?
Smoothie?
Strawberry splat.
Blueberry bang.
Splat and bang, comin' up.
Appreciate it, thanks.
It's--it's so weird.
What?
I have this weird feeling
like--like I'm supposed to...
Hug somebody.
Man, Nugs, you were at that
convention for too long.
Why don't you go and splash
some cold water on your face.
Yeah, okay.
Excuse me.
We're closed.
I know, but I forgot to pay you
guys for my last smoothie, here.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
[Knock on door]
Carly.
Hey, nice PJs.
Dude, it's Saturday
morning, I was sleeping.
I could tell.
Your hair's a mess.
Oh, well sorry for not
gettin' myself all dolled up
to answer the door.
Anyways, what's-- we got a v-mail.
From who?
Check it out.
Hey there, iCarly people.
How do I turn the camera on?
It's on, baby.
So my iCarly friends, I owe
you guys a huge thank you.
After you came to my bedroom and
talked to me, I thought about
all the things you said, and
I-- aw, do my feet look fat?
Debbie, why don't you
go make some toast?
Okay.
So you guys were right.
I was acting like a loser.
And I can't do that,
because for me to be happy
I have to be a winner.
So I have come up with a way
to Ba winner all the time.
If you wanna come see me in
action, winning, I'll be
at the fourth street athletic club,
Thursday from 10 am to noon.
I can't find any toast.
All you have is bread.
You put the bread in the toaster
and then it becomes toast
after-- later.
All right.
Our next challenger is Wilson Kreeger!
Let's go, Wilson.
I don't wanna.
[Whistling]
Wrestler number one, are you ready?
I guess.
Wrestler number two, are you ready?
Ricky Flame is always ready.
Let's go, wrestle.
[Whistling]
Unh.
Oh no, I hope I don't lose.
What's wrong with you man?
1...
Unh.
2, unh.
3.
Yeah, that's right.
And the winner is Ricky Flame.
Whoo-chow!
Wooo.
Ricky, what are you doing?
Winning.
Man, I am on fire.
Why are you wrestling kids?
'Cause I checked out the rules online.
This is a community wrestling league.
Here, read rule number 3.
Wrestling instruction and
competition, recommended for boys
ages six through ten.
See, recommended.
Doesn't say I have to
be age six to ten.
So technically, they
have to let me wrestle.
Danny Peterson, you're up.
Why are you doin' this?
I thought you loved being a chef.
No. See I realized what I
really love is winning.
[Whistling]
Wrestler number one, are you ready?
Sort of.
Wrestler number two, are you ready?
Yeah, just call it.
Wrestle.
[Whistling]
Just a second.
Oh no, I hope I can handle this one.
Come on!
It's ridiculous.
1, 2, 3...
Yeah, hooo-chows.
See, I can't lose.
Oh, yeah, but-- come
on Carly, wrestle me.
No.
Come on, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon,
no, I don't want to wrestle.
No-- you're so weird!
Come on 1, 2, 3...
[whistling]
Yeah!
19 wins, no losses, Whoo-chow!
No one can extinguish the flame.
Ha ha ha ha.
Sam Whoo-chow, Whoo-chow.
Ha, you lost.
Eat it, Flame.
Loser.
Argh!
You guys wanna go eat
some free steaks?
Shoosh yeah.
Carne.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0